so
good afternoon everyone i'm adrika and
now
it's finally time for our next question
uh question number four of the day so
now without
any further due let's quickly start with
our question
so uh you were driving a car
and noticed a bike riding triple
both of you stop at the signal you will
a lower your window and make a joke at
them
b lower lower your window and inform
that
and inform them police are checking
ahead
see you will honk loudly
or d you will lower your window and
advise them
[Music]
foreign
and
[Music]
uh and we can actually uh you know
know that how our behavior should be
there
on roads you know you can become a part
of us
in making sure that the indian roads
become safer
[Music]
to make sure that our roots are safer
we can start with this simple step uh
because versus shortest steps is a
question
however behavior should be there on
[Music]
so i will just once again repeat the
question
so you are riding a car and notice a
bike riding triple
both of you stop at the signal you
will a lower your window and make a joke
of them
b lower the window and inform
that police are checking it
or see honk loudly or d
lower your window and advise
[Music]
so you know i hope that you all had
answered
the previous questions as well and you
will be answering this question also can
you have any choice know i hope that you
all had answered previous questions
and you will be answering this question
as well as the other questions will be
which will be coming also uh you know
[Music]
you know
and then the most important thing is
that
other is question
so you can also win some exciting prizes
you know either a bike safety kit for
you and your family
[Music]
foreign
so tell your friends tell your family
about it
uh questions are there every day we are
uh every day we are having five
questions
uh and they are in a gap of two hours so
after two hours
a new question will be coming and each
question is also valid for two hours
only so
just like everything but this is our
fourth question
so after two hours of
[Music]
foreign
and you know it's very dangerous uh
uh because of so much weight
with a balance
sheet
[Music]
it is
so i will just once again repeat the
question
so you are driving a car and notice
a bike riding triple both of you stop at
the signal
you will a lower your window
and make a joke of them b
lower the window and inform that police
are checking ahead c honk loudly
or d lower your window and advise
[Music]
you know it is really easy to answer
foreign
[Music]
you know become a part of this
you know by this simple step you can
change a lot
yes you know you can tell your family
and friends also about
it you can become a part of it in making
sure
that our indian roads become safe
it's
[Music]
you know and we can also win some gifts
uh and it is really simple to answer
either you can answer it with the link
in the description
and you can also answer it from our
youtube page from our facebook page
and the results uh every day at 10 pm we
have the
we have a show called bluntly speaking
in that the results
as well as the answers will be discussed
and you can check the results on our
website
[Music]
so thank you so much everyone and
let's take this step in making sure that
our roads become safer thank you
everyone